Last week, there was a strange thing that happened when I was praying for people.
I saw a gentleman who is not a Nigerian that was arrested.
During the deliverance, the confession was so...
What I saw on the placard was not what I was looking at.
A different thing was on the placard but the problem he has is a different thing.
DELIVERANCE TIME
Prophet T.B. Joshua prays for the people at the prayer line in the power of the Holy Spirit
and encounters this man from Holland.
Let's watch what happens.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Out!
Come here!
All you have written here - you have not said the truth about your problem.
You are from where?
I am from Holland.
You are from Holland. All these statements here - spirit of anger, spirit of smoking... -
you are not saying the truth.
What I am seeing on the placard is different from what I am seeing here.
You have the spirit of robbery.
This anger leads you to rob.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come on! Stand up!
Stand up!
Stand right!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up!
Come here!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand right!
I was into a criminal life - drugs and prostitution.
You had a gang that you could go out with to...
Yes, that is true.
I was among criminals who did drugs.
I used to steal since I was young and I did drugs.
I have been to prison.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Come here!
Right. You want to do spite in the presence of God.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
He doesn't want to be delivered because he has pride.
You are delivered, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Stand up!
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Okay.
Yes, I am free. Thank You, Lord.
TESTIMONY TIME
I am Aren. I am Armenian living in Holland.
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Hallelujah!
Last Sunday, I was here in the church and the man of God T.B. Joshua told me:
He told me that what I had written on my placard was not the whole truth.
He told me that I had the spirit of stealing.
He also said that I used weapons.
What the man of God said is true.
Because in my past life, it was like that.
From an early age, I used to steal.
Between the ages of 19 and 20, I became involved with criminal activities.
I joined a big mafia system.
The mafia system I belonged to was from Russia. It was a Russian mafia.
There was also an Armenian mafia in Europe.
So, we were involved in a very big mafia system.
Don't worry. Tell me how you feel now.
Perfect.
Perfect. That spirit that was pushing you to rob, to steal -
are you still feeling this spirit in you?
I don't have the urge to steal, smoke or use drugs anymore.
Okay. What have you done to get out of this spirit of stealing and robbery in the past?
I visited different churches in Europe and also in Armenia
but that didn't help me. It did not help to get me delivered.
I wanted to be delivered but it was all to no avail.
I have been to many churches in Europe and also in Armenia, which is my country,
and tried to find a solution to get delivered but there was no way out.
I even went to Benny Hinn's crusade in Rotterdam, Holland.
When Benny Hinn came to Rotterdam in Holland, I went there with members of my church.
Nothing changed. I remained the same.
Okay. Why did you want to get out of this spirit?
I was totally and completely tired of the disgusting lifestyle I was living.
Clap for Jesus! Rise up!
Clap for Jesus!
Hallelujah. Did you listen to that?
He said he was tired.
He wanted to get out of it. He didn't want to do that again.
But how did you come across The SCOAN, T.B. Joshua, all the way from Holland?
How did you come across this church?
There was one time I was watching the miracles of Jesus Christ on YouTube.
I saw T.B. Joshua from Nigeria.
I saw all the wonders that are happening here.
And I told myself...
I told a friend of mine who is like a brother from Congo,
"Jean Pierre, my dear brother, I am totally tired of this life".
I told him, "I am going to Nigeria with you".
I told him, "I believe that as soon as I am in Nigeria, I will be totally free, in the name of Jesus!"
Aren - Deliverance Testimony
Can you see?
Sometimes when you see some of your young ones carrying a gun and robbing,
killing people, you think that they derive joy in doing it.
You never knew that they are under bondage.
There are powers that cause people to be bowed down in bondage.
Tell your neighbour.
Again.
There are powers that cause people to be bowed down in bondage.
It is not easy. A normal person would not carry a gun and start killing and stealing,
unless you are under a force, a power.
If you are not under that power, you cannot bow down for that kind of...
There are powers that cause people to be bowed down in bondage -
bondage of stealing, killing, destruction.
It is not something one can just wake up in the morning and say, "I need money".
This is why sometimes when I hear the noise all over the world that
because you are poor, that is why you are stealing,
you have no father and mother, that is why you are stealing,
they are frustrated, that is why they carry guns, kill people and destroy people -
I laugh.
There is poverty everywhere.
You can't because of poverty carry a gun.
You can't because of hardship carry a gun.
You can't because you have no father and mother carry a gun.
You can't because you are an orphan carry a gun.
You can only carry a gun and kill people when you are under the power of an evil spirit.
Actually, it was so in my life that we, the whole mafia group, were all over Europe.
How do you sleep now?
I sleep very well and peacefully like a baby.
Two days ago, at night in my dream, I heard a very weird sound.
That was two days ago?
Yes, sir.
After the deliverance?
Listen to that. He said that after the deliverance, he had a similar dream.
Okay, let's listen.
Aren - Deliverance Testimony
The sounds I heard were like that of people making love.
I went to the room and I saw those dirty things and I found them disgusting.
Immediately, I withdrew from that place.
Deliverance Testimony
This is to tell you that there is a force.
You cannot separate your loved ones by cane, by putting them in prison,
by killing them.
If you kill them, that spirit will go out and it is the flesh you are killing.
This is why the killing cannot stop robbery - it will be increasing
because the spirit in them will get out of them and enter another person and start the job.
But when you deliver them, you put them into a lock perpetually.
Deliverance Testimony
So, what message do you have for the young ones all over the world?
I am going to share with you a little part of my story.
We went in a group to Europe - France, Germany, Belgium and Holland.
We would destroy shops and gas stations.
We would also destroy cars and steal them.
Long ago, there was a former notorious mafia man who was very well known
in Europe, Russia and Armenia.
I was given this by an ex-mafia man - our leader.
Aren - Deliverance Testimony
So, you were given this ring by whom?
A former notorious mafia man who is now a minister of God. He is a brother in Christ.
This assisted you to rob, to do all sorts of things.
He gave me this ring in church and told me that it was from God.
I did not know what that meant.
I got this from our leader - it is a covenant.
Now, you are free. That is why you hand over the ring to me.
Yes.
Give me your hand.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
So you are my friend.
Okay?
Now, the covenant has been transferred.
You have a covenant with Jesus now.
So, you cannot have this ring.
How many years ago did you receive this ring?
Two to three years ago.
So, this ring - even if you hold it, you can feel some evil spirit power.
It is a talisman.
That when you have it, you will continue the job.
Nobody can get you; nobody can arrest you.
Where people cannot go, you go to and come out.
Thank you. Give advice to the whole world.
I am giving advice to the young and old who are involved in criminal activities
that this is not something you should be doing.
Don't get involved with criminals.
Do not steal.
Do not watch pornography.
Follow Jesus for the rest of your life.
Tell him that he is my friend.
Thank You, Jesus! I am free!
Thank you.
The devil is a liar! I am free, in the name of Jesus of Nazareth!
You may be seated. Thank you.
Deliverance Testimony
People of God, Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Agedu Bangawa. I am from Congo.
I am a friend of Aren.
The change I have seen in the life of Aren is very big.
During his stay here, previously, when he slept at night, I would hear him shout
because his bed was near to mine.
Now, I don't hear anything.
He sleeps like a baby.
Before, he told me, "Jean-Pierre,..."
With this ring, he can be on the bed and is somewhere.
So all these (shouts) are not there
because the spirit that worked with the ring is gone.
That is it. We want to thank you for leading him.
Thank You, Jesus!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God’s power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV – Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.